

# **ABOUT ME**

IT professional with over eight years of IT experience. I am currently attending Capella University for a PhD in Information Assurance and Cybersecurity. I have obtained multiple certifications including ITIL Foundations, CompTIA A+, Network+, Security+, SSCP, CEH, and Web Security Associate. My strengths include hard working, problem solving, critical and strategic thinking, working well in team and individual environments. Seeking an opportunity to leverage my skills in Cybersecurity.

#### CONTACT

#### PHONE:

317-995-1715

#### LinkedIn:

https://www.linkedin.com/in/mac-wells-6087b375/

#### **EMAIL:**

mac.g.wells@gmail.com

#### Address:

1082 Country Meadow Ct Franklin, IN, 46131

# **Skills**

- Metasploit
- > SQL
- ▶ nMap

# MAC WELLS BUSINESS SYSTEMS ANALYST

# **EDUCATION**

#### **Western Governors University**

February 2018 – January 2020 Bachelor of Science - Cybersecurity and Information Assurance

March 2020 – February 2021 Master of Science – Cybersecurity and Information Assurance

# Capella University

April 2021- Present PhD. Information Technology – Information Assurance and Cybersecurity

#### **WORK EXPERIENCE**

# VetsEZ – Business Analyst

August 2021 - Current

Functional analyst and technical analyst. Assist with migration projects and continuous improvement on a product in sustainment. Work with stakeholders and leadership to prioritize work and run daily, weekly, and monthly reporting. Assist with obtaining security approvals for products and writing documentation needed for security approvals.

#### CGI Federal – Senior Consultant

June 2020 – August 2021

As a tester/helpdesk associate I answered helpdesk calls multiple days a week along with answering helpdesk emails daily. Calls and emails include but not limited to, verification of document fulfillment meeting government standards, access requests, and reactivation request fulfillment. Along with testing new functionality and bug fixes. Leading 508 compliance testing and creating standard operating procedures for 508 compliance. Ensuring that CIA triad is followed. Ensure proper security has been implemented into the application.

#### **Xome Valuations - Business Systems Analyst**

November 2013 - June 2020

Functional and Technical analyst with a focus on integrations with proprietary systems. Established multiple workflows for government processes within Xome Valuations. Sole Business Analyst for integrations with experience on multi-month projects. Working with both internal and external stakeholders. Assist QA teams with testing. Assist development team with code reviews. Assist business with client calls. Elicit requirements from both clients and business stakeholders.

# Xome Valuations (formerly StreetLinks Lender Solutions) - Escalations Processing Trainer/Coach

November 2012 - December 2013

Teach, train, and Mentored Escalation Associates to do all they could for every file. Also trained new associates coming into the department about the position and different mind frame for the position.

# Xome Valuations (formerly StreetLinks Lender Solutions) - Delivery Investigations Team Lead

December 2011 - November 2012

I created this team to help with issues clients may face with the Uniform Collateral Data Portal. This included reviewing XML's to make sure that they were correct and matched what was in the appraisals and to know all the guidelines set forth by Freddy and Fannie. I also took inbound calls to assist clients with the process of connect with us for UCDP and resolving their issues they encountered for UCDP.

# **CERTIFICATIONS**

- ITIL Foundation Certificate in IT Service Management (License Number: GR750417823MW)
- CompTIA A+ ce (Credential ID: PXECS5Q3RH41Q9CJ)
- CompTIA Network+ ce (Credential ID: FQ5VNKSEZLE4Q353)
- CompTIA Project+ (Credential ID: 1TJ2ZJHEZPQEQ4CG)
- CompTIA Security+ (Credential ID: MJ8V45LMQPFQQHWN)
- CompTIA IT Operations Specialist (CIOS)
- CompTIA Secure Infrastructure Specialist (CSIS)
- CIW Web Security Associate (Credential ID: 873480)
- (ISC)<sup>2</sup> SSCP (Credential ID: 754807)
- Certified SAFe 5 Scrum Master
- EC-Council Certified Ethical Hacker (Credential ID: ECC7905418263)
- EC-Council Certified Incident Handler v2 (Credential ID: ECC7251064398)